Amadeus Folego Curriculum vitae

## AMADEUS FOLEGO DA SILVA

Born in Mauá, SP, 23/12/1988 - Single Aurora St. 787, ap. 52, São Paulo - SP, 01209-001

CONTACT INFO Email: amadeusfolego@gmail.com Phone: 55 11 95237-1152

Github: @badosu Twitter: @badosu\_

PROFILE Versatile professional, with experience developing for the web, using .Net and Ruby.

Interested in Math, Computer Science and *Hacking* in general. Has familiarity, and good learning skills, for concepts and technologies which are relevant for the web.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

11/2012 ClickARQ http://clickarq.com.br

Architecture crowdsourcing startup, where I work as the only developer.

**06/2012 - 12/2012 Codeminer42** http://codeminer42.com

Worked in several startup projects, with Ruby, Java and Python.

**01/2012 - 05/2012 Boo-box** http://boo-box.com

Technology company, in which I got touch with high scale systems.

**06/2010 - 11/2011 Betboo** http://betboo.com

Online gaming website, where I worked on projects related with expansion to other countries (Asia and Europe)

INTERESTING PROJECTS

• Borel http://rubydoc.info/gems/borel/

Created this gem to solve problems using algorithms on comparable sets.

• Audi Quattro for iPad http://vimeo.com/36426085

Developed a framework for mapping DOM elements into a bi-dimensional physics model using javascript and css-transforms extensively.

Contributions

I also have several contributions to other projects, check out my github.

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

01/2010 B.Sc. Mathematics Universidade Federal do ABC 09/2006 - 12/2010 B.Sc. Science and Technology Universidade Federal do ABC

Dynamic modelling of the Magnetic Hysteresis phenomenon
Available at (pt-br): http://www.scribd.com/doc/21709933

- Teaching Assistant
  - Multi-Variable Calculus.
  - · Vectorial and Tensorial Calculus.